

{
 "results":[
    {      
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"Which of the following statements is true about SMOG?",
        "correct_answer":"SMOG is derived from both fog and smoke",
        "incorrect_answers":["SMOG is derived from the fog","SMOG is derived from water vapour"," SMOG is derived from smoke"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"What type of precautions should be taken to survive when the ozone level is high?",
        "correct_answer":"Both drive less and stay hydrated",
        "incorrect_answers":["Drive less","Stay hydrated","Go for a long walk"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"The major photochemical smog is?",
        "correct_answer":"Chlorofluorocarbon",
        "incorrect_answers":["Hydrogen peroxide","Peroxyacetyl nitrate","All are correct"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"Which of the following diseases are caused by smog?",
        "correct_answer":"All of the above",
        "incorrect_answers":["Rickets","Bronchitis","Breathing Problems"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"How many different types of primary pollutants together contribute to about 90 per cent of the global air pollution?",
        "correct_answer":"Five",
        "incorrect_answers":["Three","None of the above","Seven"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"Smoke, fumes, ash, dust, nitric oxide and sulphur dioxide are the main sources of ?",
        "correct_answer":"Primary Pollutants.",
        "incorrect_answers":["Bio-Degradable Pollutants","Secondary pollutants","None of the above"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"Which is more in percentage in the air?",
        "correct_answer":"Nitrogen gas",
        "incorrect_answers":["Oxygen gas","Water vapour","Carbon dioxide gas"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"Which of the following gases are called Greenhouse gases?",
        "correct_answer":" Both methane and carbon dioxide",
        "incorrect_answers":["Methane","Nitrogen","Carbon dioxide"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"hard",
        "question":"Which of the following is called the secondary air pollutant?",
        "correct_answer":"Ozone",
        "incorrect_answers":["PANs","Carbon monoxide","Nitrogen Dioxide"]},
    {
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"hard",
        "question":"The particulate pollutants is?",
        "correct_answer":" Fly Ash",
        "incorrect_answers":["Ozone","Radon","Ethylene"]}
        ]
}
